# VALENTÍN NAPOLITANO



valentinnapo@gmail.com



Córdoba, Argentina



linkedin.com/in/valentinnapolitano

#### **SOFTWARE ANALYST**

I am a final-year software engineering student with a relentless drive for learning and a fervent ambition to excel in my field. I am deeply committed to honing my skills and expanding my knowledge base, with a particular interest in gaining insights from seasoned professionals with extensive industry experience.

# **EDUCATION**

2020 - Currently

### **Software Engineering**

Universidad Siglo 21

2020 - 2023

### **Software Analyst**

Universidad Siglo 21

# **LANGUAGES**

Spanish: Native

English: Advanced

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **QA Analyst**

Universidad Siglo 21, August 2022 - February 2024

Dedicated QA Analyst with expertise in designing and executing manual and automated test plans, identifying and reporting defects, and collaborating with development teams to ensure high-quality user-friendly products

## **Technical/Functional Analyst - Applications Support**

Universidad Siglo 21, August 2022 - February 2024

Technical and functional analysis aimed at performing support tasks on the institution's proprietary applications and implementing improvements on them.

#### **Atlassian Intership**

Vates, June - August 2022

Learning and practice in the Atlassian suite aimed at consulting services and projects.

# **SKILLS**

#### **PROGRAMING DATABASES OTHER** QA **DEVOPS** Java MySql Aws Selenium Web Driver Spring Boot Azure DevOps PISql Jira Software TestNG **JavaScript** Terraform MongoDB Scrum **Automation Testing** NodeJs Docker Postman Data Driven Testing ExpressJS Kubernetes Analysis and software design **Functional Testing** (GKE-AKS-EKS)

Jenkins Ansible